<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publication on DAACS</title>
    <link>https://daacs.net/tags/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publication on DAACS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daacs.net/tags/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Bryer to be panelist for World Future Forum</title>
      <link>https://daacs.net/blog/2019/04/2019-04-24-worldfutureforum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daacs.net/blog/2019/04/2019-04-24-worldfutureforum/</guid>
      <description>Future Review Panel: Approaches to Studying Student Success in Higher Education Thursday, April 24, 11:25am to 12:10pm, Chicago
This panel will highlight the work that is published in Future Review, our publication. Two of the first authors to publish in this journal will discuss their work on student success. The panel features both quantitative and qualitative research, and highlights the different ways of conceptualizing student success in higher education. Panelists will also discuss how their research can be used by practitioners in higher education, and why they chose Future Review as a venue for their research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Validity Evidence of the Internal Structure of the DAACS Self-Regulated Learning Survey</title>
      <link>https://daacs.net/blog/2019/04/2019-04-01-futurereview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daacs.net/blog/2019/04/2019-04-01-futurereview/</guid>
      <description>Validity Evidence of the Internal Structure of the DAACS Self-Regulated Learning Survey Authors: Angela M. Lui, David Franklin Jr., Diana Akhmedjanova, Guher Gorgun, Jason Bryer, Heidi L. Andrade, and Timothy Cleary
Abstract The Diagnostic Assessment and Achievement of College Skills (DAACS) online system assesses newly enrolled college students’ skills in reading, writing, mathematics, and self-regulated learning, and provides individualized feedback and links to resources. The purpose of this study is to examine validity evidence regarding the internal structure of the DAACS Self-Regulated Learning (SRL) self-report survey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>